Today we opened it for your visit,
because this one was designed specifically
for the Paris Olympics and was
hosted at Casa Italia.  Being Casa
Italia we wanted to create a
textile fresco of how we see Taler and it is
precisely the textile manufacturing that
becomes artistic.  It's a tribute to
our Italy, designed with
artificial intelligence and helped by
Riccardo Donadon of H Farm who taught us how
to use
artificial intelligence.  We are Venetians and so there is
the Venetian food par excellence which is
risi e bisi.  There's the geographical location, the
Rialto Bridge, there's Corner who is the
first woman to graduate in the world and then there's
innovation, the Veneto
of innovation, vertical farms and every
region always has its saints, its
poets.  You see that the factory is an artist
at